[
    {
        "question": "What is the world's largest ocean?",
        "options": [
            "Pacific",
            "Atlantic",
            "Indian",
            "Arctic"
        ],
        "answer": "Pacific"
    },
    {
        "question": "In a leap year, how many days are there?",
        "options": [
            "Three hundred sixty-four",
            "Three hundred sixty-five",
            "Three hundred sixty-six",
            "Three hundred sixty-seven"
        ],
        "answer": "Three hundred sixty-six"
    },
    {
        "question": "France's capital city is what?",
        "options": [
            "London",
            "Paris",
            "Berlin",
            "Rome"
        ],
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "The strongest human muscle is which one?",
        "options": [
            "Bicep",
            "Calf",
            "Heart",
            "Quadriceps"
        ],
        "answer": "Heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "The United States uses what currency?",
        "options": [
            "Euro",
            "Dollar",
            "Yen",
            "Yuan"
        ],
        "answer": "Dollar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Earth's tallest mountain is which one?",
        "options": [
            "Mount Everest",
            "K2",
            "Kangchenjunga",
            "Lhotse"
        ],
        "answer": "Mount Everest"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is not a primary color?",
        "options": [
            "Red",
            "Yellow",
            "Blue",
            "Green"
        ],
        "answer": "Green"
    },
    {
        "question": "The largest land animal on Earth is which?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant",
            "Giraffe",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Earth has how many moons?",
        "options": [
            "Zero",
            "One",
            "Two",
            "Three"
        ],
        "answer": "One"
    },
    {
        "question": "What search engine am I using to answer your questions?",
        "options": [
            "Bing",
            "DuckDuckGo",
            "Google",
            "Yahoo"
        ],
        "answer": "Google"
    }
]